pvinsights.com 2010-05-07

# PV Insights: All Solar PV Price

This privacy policy describes how PV Insights. and its affiliates will treat the personal information received about you when you visit PV Insights (home page at PVInsights.com)

**Information We Collect**

**We Collect:** When you register for membership or other benefits, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, e-mail address and credit-card information, and other information such as facts about your computers, profession and similar information. 

**Surveys:** We may conduct occasional surveys and other customer research. These are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate. 

**Web Site Usage Information:** We automatically collect IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit the Services. This information helps us, among other things, evaluate how you use and navigate our web sites. 

**How We Use Information Collected**

We may use information in the following ways: 

  * For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to process, validate and verify your registration. 
  * To send you notifications about your accounts or transactions with us and to otherwise contact you with information that we believe will be of interest to you. 
  * To notify you about our products, services and special offers or those of our advertisers. 
  * To enhance or develop features, products and services. 
  * To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. 
  * To personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences. 

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of PV Insights, unless we tell you otherwise when we collect the information or you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us. Subject to the foregoing, we may allow select companies to send you materials about their products and services.

We may combine the information that we collect from you on the Services with information that you provide to us in connection with your use of our other products, services and web sites or information we collect from third parties.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Terms of Service and other rights (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights) or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or appropriate in connection with or as the result of a change in ownership of all or a portion of the Services as the result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company. We also may disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so. 

**Review and Correction**

You may review and update the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us by contacting Customer Service at [support@PVInsights.com](mailto:mwsupportcs@marketwatch.com). PV Insights members also may update their information by signing on to their accounts and visiting your Account.? (Please note that if you have registered more than one email address with us, each email address constitutes a distinct account, and you must update your information in each account separately.)

While we strive to process your requests as quickly as possible, please allow for reasonable time for us to process your updates.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We employ cookie technology to, among other things, allow you to move quickly through our Services, facilitate the login processes and allow you to personalize and store your settings. We also use cookies to collect site usage information, estimate our total audience size and traffic, and help us improve our sites experiences by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to users. 

You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser in your computer. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Without cookies you can visit our Services and read some articles, but you will not be able to use the products or services that require you to sign in and you may not be able to take full advantage of some of the useful and convenient features, such as saving and accessing your customized news and portfolio settings and other personalized options. 

Other cookies that you may receive during your sessions here are from third-party service providers or third-party ad servers. Third-party ad servers collect and use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Services and other web sites in order to present advertisements that may be of interest to you.

We also use web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) on our Services in order to recognize users and assess traffic patterns, and we include web beacons and cookies in our e-mail messages, including newsletters, to among other things, count how many e-mail messages have been opened.

**Ads for the Services**

When you view an ad for the Services on other sites, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The Services and our advertising company may also use web beacons (invisible images often referred to as pixel tags or clear GIFs) to note which pages you visit after viewing our ads. The information that is collected through the use of these images is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts. 

**Third Party Information**

If you choose to use our service to send a story to a friend, we will ask you for your email address and your friend�s email address in order to fulfill your request and let the recipient know who sent the story.

**Security**

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited-access servers. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers. If you choose to make a purchase through our website, during your purchase the personal and credit card information you transmit over the internet will be encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

**Data Retention**

We retain your information for as long as necessary to permit us to use it for the purposes that we have communicated to you and comply with applicable law or regulations. 

**Transfer to Other Countries**

Your information may be stored and processed in any other country by using the Services, you consent to the transfer of information outside of your country. 

**Specific Features**

**Interactive Tools.** **** Certain features of the Services give you an opportunity to interact with us and other members. These may include message boards, submitting a letter to the editor, creating community profiles, creating virtual stock portfolios, and rating, tagging and commenting on articles. When you use these features you should be aware that any information you submit there, including your name, location and e-mail address, may be publicly available to others. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit through these interactive features. 

**Third-Party and Corporate Memberships.** **** If your access to the Services, or any part of the Services, is provided by your employer or a third party, we may notify your employer or that third party when you access the Services. In doing so, we may reveal limited amounts of your personally identifiable information such as your name or email address. Your employer or the third party providing your access may provide us with limited amounts of personal information about you to facilitate your access to the Services and so that we may identify you when providing it with user and usage information. 

**Policy Modifications**

When we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on the home page of this site that the policy has been updated and by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated.
